

PARTH CHOUDHARY

ECE Student At DTU

PROFILE

I am a 2nd year student at Delhi Technological University (Formerly DCE). Where I am pursuing Electronics and Communication Engineering. I have invested my time in learning various skills like Web Development, Machine Learning and data structures and algorithms.

My passion is to work under this type of domains that's why I am searching for internship opportunities in this field so that I can enhance my knowledge and experience.

CONTACT

Email

parthch.777@gmail.com

Phone

+91 9310126360

Website

pch7.github.io/intro

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

Javascript

C, C++ and Python

Web Designer

Problem Solving

Data Structures & Algorithms

HOBBIES

Playing Outdoor games, Travelling and reading Current Affairs.

LANGUAGES

Hindi

English

French

EDUCATION

Matriculation, Flora Dale School

Apr 2017 - May 2018

I have passed matriculation with 89.6%.

10+2, Flora Dale School

Apr 2019 - Apr 2020

I have scored 92% in 10+2 Boards.

Bachelor Of Technology, Delhi Technological University

Nov 2020 - May 2024

Now I am in 4th semester and I have got 9.1 SGPA in 1st , 9.4 in 2nd and 8.64 in 3rd Semester.

EXPERIENCE

Web Designer

Apr 2021 - Jun 2021

I was selected as web designer in 2 societies of DTU - DelTechMUN DTU and INNOVA DTU. But didn't do any recognisable work.

Corporate Executive

Jul 2021 - Oct 2021

I have joined ICAPIE DTU for few months, where I got a chance to work as a corporate executive to raise funds for the society. I have talked to some companies to sponsor our society for differnt programs but didn't able to get any.

INTERNSHIPS

Till Now, I haven't got any internship so there isn't anything to show.